Guide to the Sarabande Books Records, 1990-2022 RL.01137
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sarabande Books records
1990-2022
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sarabande Books
RL.01137
123.5 Linear Feet
Sarabande Books is a non-profit literary press publishing poetry and fiction. The Sarabande Books records include materials documenting the founding of the company as well as yearly publishing materials.
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
In addition, some of the materials in this collection are not immediately accessible, because they require further processing before use.
Provenance
The Sarabande Books Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 2000-2003; further annual accessions were added to the collection from 2005-2022.
Biographical Note
Sarabande Books is a non-profit literary press publishing poetry and fiction. It was established in 1994 by Sarah Gorham in Louisville, Kentucky.
Collection Overview
This collection (accession #2000-0306) (4150 items, dated 1992-1996) documents the founding of the company. Many files mention editor and president Sarah Gorham and include start-up files, correspondence and author files, marketing materials, financial records, and other materials generated by the press. Also includes Gorham's memoir written during the first days of the press; files on prizes offered by the press (the Mary McCarthy Prize for short fiction and the Kathryn A. Morthon Prize for poetry); correspondence with authors Jane Mead, Lee Martin, Richard Frost, Sharon Bryan, Laura Jenson, Medbh McGuckian, and Liliana Ursu; and correspondence with Sallie Bingham about the formation of the press. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Addition (2001-0022) (2911 items, 4.4 linear feet; dated 1996-1997) continues to document the company's activities. Materials include correspondence files; author files; sales and marketing files; 24 color and 4 black-and-white photographs; 11 electronic (computer) files; and material relating to Sarabande's non-profit operations from 1996 to 1997. Much of the correspondence tracks letters to and from Sallie Bingham and Sarah Gorham. Authors represented include Dick Allen, Brian Griffin, Sharon Solwitz, Belle Waring, and Baron Wormser.
Addition (2002-0062) (2260 items, 6.3 linear feet; dated 1996-1998) comprises primarily author binders, files, and correspondence (1996-1998); and marketing and sales records, including examples of advertisements and reviews (1998). Also includes correspondence between Sallie Bingham and Sarah Gorham (1998); poetry and fiction galleys; documents related to the press' nonprofit activities, including 2 audio cassette tapes and paper records documenting board meetings (1998); 2 color and 10 black-and-white photographs and 1 black-and-white negative; and 18 electronic (computer) files originally received on one 3.5" diskette. Authors represented include Cathleen Hagenston, James Kimbrell, Stefanie Marlis, Shara McCallum, Jean Valentine, and Kate Walbert.
Addition (2003-0021) (2,300 items, 5.30 linear feet; dated 1995-2002) consists largely of author files (1997-2000) and printed material comprising journals and review publications (1998-1999). Also includes office correspondence (1995-2002); sales analyses, grant proposals, and marketing files (1996-2001); and documents related to conferences and events, special projects, board meetings, and nonprofit activities.
Addition (2004-0018) (4000 items, 6.6 lin. ft.; dated 1999-2001) includes author binders and files, correspondence, financial and marketing archives, and manuscript galleys. This accession is closed to researchers.
Addition (2005-0019) (3695 items, 6.0 lin. ft.; dated 2000-2001) primarily comprises authors' binders, including incoming and outgoing correspondence, as well as typescript drafts and galleys. Also includes reviews, press releases, and advertisements; notes from sales conferences and board meetings; consortium sales analyses; a non-profit activity file; and organizational materials for Sarabande-in-Education, a website program for college students and teachers. This accession is closed to researchers.
Addition (2006-0025) (3,750 items, 6.0 lin. ft.; dated 2001-2002) comprises correspondence, drafts, galleys, marketing and biographical files, contracts, press releases, and book reviews. This accession is closed to researchers.
Addition (2007-0041) (6,000 items, 9.2 lin. ft.; dated 1996-2003) contains autographed books, authors' files, manuscripts, the contents of author binders, marketing files, board meeting files, nonprofit activitiy files, Lila Wallace materials, sales kits, a Writer's Almanac CD, and a Sallie Bingham rehearsal tape for Short Fiction Series.
Addition (2008-0028) (4,500 items; 6.0 lin. ft.; dated 2004-2005) contains author files, correspondence, marketing files and galleys for books published in 2004-2005. Also included are 2 CDR's of the Writer's Almanac.
Addition (2009-0092) (8325 items; 11.1 lin. ft.; dated 1998-2009) includes administrative files, book reviews, press releases, author files and correspondence, and manuscripts and drafts from authors published by Sarabande.
Addition (2010-0028) (9000 items; 12.0 lin. ft.; dated 2001-2010) includes administrative files, Sarabande correspondence with authors, author files, poetry and fiction finalists, and various book reviews and advertisements.
Addition (2011-0076) (6750 items; 9.0 lin. ft.; dated 1994-2011) includes materials from conferences, non-profit activities, grants, correspondence, marketing, staffing, finances, and author files.
Addition (2012-0046) (3188 items; 4.5 lin. ft.; dated 2006-2011) includes correspondence, publicity files, author files, and manuscripts.
Addition (2013-0158) (5625 items; 7.5 lin. ft.; dated 2006-2012) includes author files, reviews, manuscripts, author correspondence and administrative materials.
Addition (2015-0150) (900 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 2008-2014) includes administrative materials and author correspondence, foundation research and correspondence, and author files.
Addition (2015-0151) (2250 items; 4.5 lin. ft.; dated 2009-2015) includes administrative files, author files and author binders.
Addition (2016-0311) (3.0 lin. ft; dated 2011-2016) consists chiefly of author files. Also contains files related to prizes and awards.
Addition (2018-0011) (4.0 lin. ft.; dated 2016-2018) consists of publicity and author files that contain drafts of recently published works.
Addition (2019-0093) (1.5 lin. ft.; dated 2015-2017) consists of author files, including Sallie Bingham's publishing agreement and drafts of works.
Addition 2021-0075 (1.5 lin. ft.; dated 2019-2020) includes author files for books published in 2019 and 2020, Sarabande Writing Labs brochure, 2019 and 2020 catalogs, press releases and reviews for 2019 and 2020 books, and annual reports.
Addition 2022-0084 (3.0 lin. ft.; dated 1990 and 2010-2022) includes author files, Sarabande Writing Labs anthologies, catalogs, promotional ephemera, a poetry broadsides.
Materials Cataloged Separately
Signed copies in paper and cloth and galleys of the following books were removed from accession #2001-0022 and cataloged separately:
Last Call
Ode to the Cold War
Sparkman in the Sky
Dark Blonde
When
Blood and Milk
Signed copies in paper and cloth of the following books were removed from accession #2002-0062 and cataloged separately:
Entire Dilemma
Equipoise
Gatehouse Heaven
A Gram of Mars
Rife
Taking Eden
Where She Went
Signed copies removed from Accession 2012-0046 to be cataloged separately:
This Is Not Your City
Cold War
Hoodwinked
The Cows
Small Fires
Mending: New & Selected
Signed copies in paper and cloth of the following books were removed from accession #2002-0062 and cataloged separately:
Entire Dilemma
Equipoise
Gatehouse Heaven
A Gram of Mars
Rife
Taking Eden
Where She Went
Signed copies removed from Accession 2013-0158 to be cataloged separately:
Let Me Clear My Throat
Clangings
Book Of Dog
Syzygy, Beauty
The Children
Something In My Eye
Rough Likeness
Rise
City Of Poetry
Small presses -- Kentucky; Women publishers -- Kentucky; Small presses -- Southern States; Publishers and publishing -- United States; Black-and-white photographs; Gorham, Sarah, 1954 -- Correspondence; Machine-readable records; Bingham, Sallie -- Correspondence; Audiocassettes; Color photographs; Authors and publishers -- United States; Black-and-white negatives; McGuckian, Medbh, 1950-; Mead, Jane, 1958-; Marlis, Stefanie, 1951-; McCallum, Shara, 1972-; Halme, Kathleen; Lee, Martin; Griffin, Brian, 1957-; Hagenston, Becky, 1967-; Calbert, Cathleen; Frost, Richard, 1929-; Bingham, Sallie; Bryan, Sharon; Allen, Dick, 1939-; Wormser, Baron; Waring, Belle, 1951-; Ursu, Liliana, 1949-; Solwitz, Sharon, 1945-; Walbert, Kate, 1961-; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; Valentine, Jean; Skinner, Jeffrey; Sarabande Books
- Accession (2000-0306), 1994-1996
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restriction: Budget files (box 6) may not be used without permission of the president of Sarabande Books for a period of 25 years from creation.
  - Start-Up Files (Box 1)
    - Sarabande Books - Sarah (Box 1)
    - Start-Up - Sarah (Box 1)
    - Office Start-Up (Box 1)
    - Bar Codes for Cover (Box 1)
    - Design - Logo (Box 1)
    - 501-C-3 Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Incorporation Documents (Box 1)
    - Nonprofit Application (Box 1)
    - Sales Tax and Bulk Mail Application (Box 1)
    - Sarabande History (Box 1)
    - Trademark Registration (Box 1)
    - Resources: Books, Subscriptions, Dues (Box 1)
    - Production-General (Box 1)
  - Staffing and Services
    - Staffing Inquiries (Box 1)
    - Interview Notes (Box 1)
    - Marketing Director 1994 - High/Middle Low, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Late Marketing Applications 1994 (Box 1)
    - Distributors - General (Box 1)
    - Distributors - Inland (Box 1)
    - Distributors - National Book Network (Box 1)
    - Distributors - Publishers Group West (Box 1)
    - Distributors - University (Box 1)
    - Wholesalers and Warehousers (Box 1)
    - Typesetters (Box 1)
    - Sales Terms (Box 1)
  - Contests
    - Contests - Startup (Box 1)
    - Contest 1995 (Box 1)
    - Contest 1996 (Box 1)
    - Fiction Finalist (Box 1)
  - Nonprofit Files
    - Board Meeting 1996 (Box 1)
    - Board Meeting 1995 (Box 1)
    - Nonprofit Activity 1996 (Box 1)
    - Nonprofit Activity 1995 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence Files
    - American Voice Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Gorham/Gallagher Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Gorham/Bingham Correspondence 1996, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Gorham/Bingham Correspondence 1995, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Gorham/Bingham Correspondence 1994 and earlier, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Sallie's Book, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Straight Man MS., 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Author Files
    - Jane Mead, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Lee Martin (Box 2)
    - Martin - Edited Stories (Box 2)
    - Martin - Sub-rights (Box 2)
    - Richard Frost (Box 2)
      Scope and Contents note
      Electronic files included under this entry were copied onto server. See reference archivist for assistance.
    - Sharon Bryan (Box 2)
    - Laura Jenson (Box 2)
    - Medbh McGuckian (Box 2)
    - Liliana Ursu (Box 2)
  - Author Books, signed copies of Mead, Martin, Frost, Bryan (Box 2)
  - Letters In and Out, 1996 January- 1996 February, 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Letters In and Out, 51 folders (Box 3)
    - 1996 March-1996 December (Box 3)
    - 1995 (Box 3)
    - 1994 September-1994 December (Box 3)
  - Letters Out Log Book (Box 4)
    Attention: Copy newsprint onto acid-free paper before use.
  - Press kit (Box 4)
  - Marketing Archives
    - 1994 (Box 4)
    - 1995 (Box 4)
    - 1996, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Catalog 1996 Fall (Box 4)
  - ABA 1996 (Box 4)
  - AWP Conference 1996 (Box 4)
  - Sales Conference, 1996 December (Box 4)
  - Sales Conference 1995 (Box 4)
  - Newsletter Masters (Box 4)
  - Stationery file (Box 4)
  - Galleys and brochures (Box 4)
  - Journals and newspapers with Sarabande ad space or book reviews (Box 4)
  - Journals continued (Box 5)
  - Sarabande Memoir, Gorham (Box 6)
  - Sales Analysis by Title (Box 6)
  - Marketing Director - Top (Box 6)
  - Kristin Herbert (Box 6)
  - Budgets 1994-1996 (Box 6)
    RESTRICTED
  - Neighbor Blood - digital files, circa 1988-1995; One 3.5 inch floppy disk containing 6 digital files (102 KB) (Digital-materials RL01137-SET-0001)
- Accession (2001-0022), 1997
  - Nonprofit Files, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Board Meeting (Box 1)
    - Nonprofit Activity (Box 1)
    - CLMP Judging-Nonprofit Activity (Box 1)
    - KY State Arts Council (Box 1)
    - Witter Bynner, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
    - NH State Arts Council (Box 1)
  - Office Correspondence Files: Letters In and Out, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Bingham-Gorham Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Author Files
    - Belle Waring (Box 1)
    - Baron Wormser (Box 1)
    - Brian Griffin (Box 1)
    - Dick Allen (Box 2)
    - Last Call, misc. (Gorham, Skinner, editors) (Box 2)
    - Last Call, research (Box 2)
    - Last Call, education (Box 2)
    - Last Call, mailing list (Box 2)
    - Last Call, Louisville event (Box 2)
    - Sharon Solwitz (Box 2)
    - Ray Young Bear (Box 2)
    - Jenny Offill (Box 2)
  - Signed copies, cloth and paper, of various books (Box 2)
    [removed for individual cataloging; see list at end of container list for titles]
  - Marketing and sales files, 1997
    - Ads and reviews (Box 2)
    - Galleys (Box 2)
      [Removed to box 5]
    - Misc. marketing (Box 2)
      Includes catalogs, brochures, postcards, newsletters, t-shirts, and journals in which advertisements or reviews of Sarabande Books' publications appeared.
      [Journals removed to boxes 5 and 6]
    - ABA (Box 2)
    - AWP (Box 3)
    - May sales conference (Box 3)
    - December sales consultation (Box 3)
    - Consortium material: monthly newsletters/sales conference packets, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
    - Consortium sales analysis by title: monthly and yearly (Box 4)
    - Sarabande Books sales kits, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
    - Subscribers (Box 4)
    - Galleys (uncorrected proofs) of Last Call, Ode to the Cold War, Sparkman in the Sky, Dark Blonde, When, and Blood and Milk. (Box 5)
    - Journals in which advertisements or reviews of Sarabande Books' publications appeared (Box 5)
    - Journals in which advertisements or reviews of Sarabande Books' publications appeared (Box 6)
  - Training to be an Astronaut: Stories by Brian Griffin (Draft), 1996; One 3.5 inch floppy disk containing 11 files (328 KB) (Digital-materials RL01137-SET-0001)
  - Dick Allen, Ode to the Cold War: Poems New and Selected, Microsoft Word 6.0.1, PowerMAC 7500, 1996 May; One 3.5 inch floppy disk containing one file (246KB) (Digital-materials RL01137-SET-0001)
- Accession (2002-0062), 1996-1998
  - Author binders, 1996-1997
    - Jane Mead, 1996 June (Box 1)
    - Sharon Bryan, 1997 May (Box 1)
    - Last Call, 1997 January (Box 1-2)
    - Lee Martin, 1996 June (Box 2)
    - Richard Frost, 1996 November (Box 2)
    - Brian Griffin, 1997 October (Box 3)
    - Belle Waring, 1997 November (Box 3)
    - Baron Wormser ( When), 1997 November (Box 3)
    - Dick Allen, 1997 April (Box 3)
    - Sharon Solwitz, 1997 May (Box 3)
  - Author files/correspondence, 1998
    - Shara McCallum (Box 4)
      Includes poetry manuscripts.
    - Jean Valentine (Box 4)
    - Robert Clinton (Box 4)
    - Stefanie Marlis (Box 4)
      Includes poetry manuscript.
    - James Kimbrell (Box 4)
    - Kate Walbert (Box 4)
      Includes edit of last chapter manuscript.
    - Kathleen Halme (Box 4)
    - Becky Hagenston (Box 4)
    - Cathleen Calbert (Box 4)
    - Calbert--additional poems (Box 4)
    - Incoming and outgoing office correspondence, 1998 March (Box 4)
    - Incoming and outgoing office correspondence, 1998 April-December (Box 5)
    - Incoming and outgoing office correspondence, 1998 January-February (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, Bingham/Gorman (Box 6)
  - Marketing and sales archives
    - Poetry contest entry logbook, 1996-1998 (Box 6)
    - Reviews and ads, including magazines and clippings, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Reviews and ads, including magazines and clippings, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Poetry Galleys (Box 8)
      - Taking Eden (Box 8)
      - Rife (Box 8)
      - Gatehouse Heaven (Box 8)
      - Entire Dilemma (Box 8)
      - Equipoise (Box 8)
    - Fiction Galleys
      - Where She Went (Box 8)
      - A Gram of Mars (Box 8)
    - 1998 Marketing (Box 8)
      Includes newsletters, brochures, and the 1998-1999 catalog.
    - Rife purchase incentive (Box 8)
    - 1998 sales kits, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1998 subscribers (Box 8)
    - ABA [BookExpo America] 1998 (Box 8)
    - AWP [Literary Magazine and Small Press Conference] 1998 (Box 8)
    - Consortium Pre-Sales Conference, 1997-1998 (Box 8-9)
    - Sales conference, 1998Spring and December (Box 9)
    - Consortium sales analysis by title: monthly and yearly, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Nonprofit files, 1998
    - Board meeting, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Nonprofit activity, 1998 (Box 9)
    - CSU [Cleveland State University] Lecture (Box 9)
    - KY State Arts Council Judge (Box 9)
    - Submission list master/publication resource list (Box 9)
    - 1998 Kentucky newsletter (Box 9)
    - KY State Arts Council (Box 9)
    - Witter Bynner [Foundation for Poetry], [funding request], 1998 (Box 9)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, [funding proposal], 1998 (Box 9)
  - Definitions, 1997; One 3.5 inch floppy disk containing 7 folders, 41 files (192 KB) (Digital-materials RL01137-SET-0001)
- Accession (2003-0021), 1998-2002
  Budget files (Boxes 7 and 8) are restricted and may not be used without permission of the president of Sarabande Books for a period of 25 years from creation.
  Some of the materials in this collection are not immediately accessible, because they require further processing before use. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the Rubenstein Library to use this collection.
  - Contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    - Author files
      - Becky Hagenston (Box 1)
      - Kathleen Halme (Box 1)
      - Michael Burkard (Box 1)
      - Kate Walbert (Box 1)
  - Contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    - Author files
      - James Kimbrell (Box 2)
      - Stephanie Marlis (Box 2)
      - Robert Clinton (Box 2)
      - Baron Wormser (Box 2)
      - Judith Slater (Box 2)
      - James Baker Hall (Box 2)
      - Aleida Rodriguez (Box 2)
      - Robin Lippincott (Box 2)
    - The Beach Book: Correspondence, author requests/permissions (Box 2)
  - Contents of Box 3: (Box 3)
    - Office Correspondence: 1999 Sept.-1999 Dec. (Box 3)
  - Contents of Box 4: (Box 4)
    - Office Correspondence: 1999 Mar.-1999 Sept. (Box 4)
    - Bingham/Graham Correspondence (Box 4)
  - Contents of Box 5: (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Nickole Brown's Letter Log 9/1/95-2/27/02 (Box 5)
    - Marketing Archives, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Printed material: Journals, Book Catalogues, 1999 Jan.-July (Box 5)
  - Contents of Box 6: (Box 6)
    - Marketing Archives, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Printed material: Journals, 1999 Apr.-Nov. (Box 6)
  - Contents of Box 7: (Box 7)
    - Printed material: Journals, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
    - Grants, Non Profit (Box 7)
    - Analysis of sales, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Contents of Box 8: (Box 8)
    - Conferences, events, and projects, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Grant proposals (Box 8)
    - Non profit papers (Box 8)
    - Sales Summaries, 1996-2001 (Box 8)
  - Contents of Box 9: (Box 9)
    - Book Review journals and newspapers, 1998 Dec.-1999 Aug. (Box 9)
- Accession (2004-0018), 1999-2001; 11 boxes
  Addition (2004-0018) (4000 items, 6.6 lin. ft.; dated 1999-2001) includes author binders and files, correspondence, financial and marketing archives, and manuscript galleys. This accession is closed to researchers.
- Accession (2005-0019), 2000-2001; 9 boxes
  Addition (2005-0019) (3695 items, 6.0 lin. ft.; dated 2000-2001) primarily comprises authors' binders, including incoming and outgoing correspondence, as well as typescript drafts and galleys. Also includes reviews, press releases, and advertisements; notes from sales conferences and board meetings; consortium sales analyses; a non-profit activity file; and organizational materials for Sarabande-in-Education, a website program for college students and teachers. This accession is closed to researchers.
- Accession (2006-0025), 2001-2002; 10 boxes
  Addition (2006-0025) (3,750 items, 6.0 lin. ft.; dated 2001-2002) comprises correspondence, drafts, galleys, marketing and biographical files, contracts, press releases, and book reviews. This accession is closed to researchers.
- Accession (2007-0041), 1999-2003; 16 boxes
  Addition (2007-0041) (6,000 items, 9.2 lin. ft.; dated 1996-2003) contains autographed books, authors' files, manuscripts, the contents of author binders, marketing files, board meeting files, nonprofit activitiy files, Lila Wallace materials, sales kits, a Writer's Almanac CD, and a Sallie Bingham rehearsal tape for Short Fiction Series.
  - Author files, manuscripts, signed books, and galleys, 2003 (Box 1-3)
    - Kate Gadbow, Pushed to Shore (Box 1-3)
    - Dick Allen, The Day Before (Box 1-3)
    - Sharon Bryan and William Olsen, eds., Planet on the Table (Box 1-3)
    - James Tate, Lost River (Box 1-3)
    - Marjorie Sandor, Portrait of my Mother Who Posed Nude in Wartime (Box 1-3)
    - Mark Turpin, Hammer (Box 4-6)
    - Sharon Solwitz, Bloody Mary (including file of additional Solwitz stories) (Box 4-6)
    - Carrie St. George Comer, The Unrequited (Box 4-6)
    - Arthur Vogelsang, Left Wing of a Bird (Box 4-6)
    - Debra Nystrom, Torn Sky (Box 4-6)
  - Author binders, 2002 (Box 7-8)
    - Joseph Caldwell, Bread for the Baker's Child (Box 7-8)
    - Brock Clarke, What We Won't Do (Box 7-8)
    - Frank Bidart, Music Like Dirt (Box 7-8)
    - James Kimbrell and Yu Jung-yul, eds., Three Poets of Modern Korea (Box 7-8)
    - James Hall, Praeder's Letters (Box 7-8)
  - Robin Lippincott, Mr. Dalloway, 1999 (Box 7-8)
  - Cathleen Calbert, Bad Judgment, 1999 (Box 7-8)
  - Ralph Angel, Twice Removed, 2001 (Box 7-8)
  - Marketing and miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Reviews (Box 8-11)
    - Advertisements (Box 8-11)
    - Honors (Box 8-11)
    - Miscellaneous marketing (Box 8-11)
    - Sales kits (Box 8-11)
    - Contest, 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Public relations (Box 8-11)
    - Sallie Bingham rehearsal tape for short fiction series (Box 8-11)
    - Writer's Almanac CD (Box 8-11)
    - Nonprofit activity file, 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Gorham Kentucky Arts Council judging, 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Rotary Club, November 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Party, September 2002 (Box 8-11)
    - Book expo, 2002 (Box 8-11)
    - AWP, 2002-2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Sales and presales, 2002 and Spring 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Board meetings, Spring 2003 and October 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Office correspondence, 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Gorham correspondence, January-June 2002 (Box 8-11)
    - Acquisitions, 2001-2002 and 2003-2004 (Box 8-11)
    - Woodford Reserve, 2003 (Box 8-11)
    - Consortium Catalogue and Tipsheets, 1996-1997 (Box 8-11)
    - Consortium sales analysis by title and fast reports, 2003 (Box 8-11)
  - Lila Wallace materials (Box 12-13)
  - Sales kits (Box 14-16)
- Accession (2008-0028), 2004-2005; 10 boxes
  Addition (2008-0028) (4,500 items; 6.0 lin. ft.; dated 2004-2005) contains author files, correspondence, marketing files and galleys for books published in 2004-2005. Also included are 2 CDR's of the Writer's Almanac.
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Author files (Box 2)
    - Brian Leung (Box 2)
    - Lonse Glück (Box 2)
    - Baron Wormser 3 (Box 2)
    - Zack Rogow (Box 2)
    - Mark Jarman (Box 2)
    - Steven Cramer (Box 2)
    - Neeca Vatswani (Box 2)
    - Pee Wee Watson (Box 2)
  - Board meetings (Box 2)